slot.com 2019-04-15

# Privacy Policy | Slot.com

**Slot.com wishes to inform his website and/or mobile application users (from now on “website”) his Privacy Policy, informing, among others, in a transparent way, all the processing that we make with your data, the purposes for which we treat them and the rights you have as a user to exercise over your personal data.**

We inform you that when you access to our website you become a User. As a User, you declarte that you are over the legal age and you have the necessary legal capacity to understand and fully accept this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our Cookies Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Slot.com

We hope that you enjoy the experience in Slot.com.

1\. WHO IS THE RESPONSIBLE FOR YOUR PERSONAL DATA?

  * _Identity:_ SOCIAL GAMES ONLINE, S.L (from now on “Slot.com”), with CIF B98549611e registered in Registro Mercantil de Barcelona, tomo 49847; Folio 22; Hoja B-440114, is responsible of the treatment of the personal data that you are providing us.

  * _Postal adress:_ Ctra de Castellar, n.338, C.P 08226 Terrassa (Barcelona).

  * _Delegate contact of Data Protection:_ [protecciondedatos@socialgamesonline.io](mailto:protecciondedatos@socialgamesonline.io)

If you wish, you can get in touch with us through the online contact form on our website https://www.slot.com/contact.

2\. WHAT IS THE DATA AND THE TREATMENT OF PERSONAL NATURE?

Are those data that identifies or allows to identify a person. For example, the data that can identify directly a person are the first and last name, while the Identity Card can lead to identify the person. The personal data includes information like the telephone number, email address, date of birth, gender, etc, it can include the numerical identifiers like the IP of your computer as well as the information that it’s obtained through the cookies.

A treatment of a personal nature is any operation or group of operation that we do on your personal data, for example, the collection, recording, storage, use and communication of your data.

3\. WHAT PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT?

It’s necessary that to enjoy the games that Slot.com offers you, you have to be registered in our website and create and account that allows you to enjoy the advantages of a real user such as;

  * Be able to send friend requests to other users of Slot.com.

  * Visualize all the achievements of our games.

  * Visualize the coins that you purchase.

  * Change the language if you wish.

  * Your profile picture if you wish.

  * Change the setting for sending electronic communications.

To register we only need your email address, if you want to register through your email address. However, if you decide to play with Facebook, we will ask you to sign in to your Facebook account (email address and/or mobile number and password). Once you have signed in into your account of Facebook, this social network will ask for your permission to share with us your email address, your friends list, "likes", and other public information on this social network.

Once you have registered, we will give you a unique identifier that will be associated to an account, that will be your profile. This profile will be specific for the players of [www.slot.com](http://www.slot.com/). Other players will be able to see your progress on the game, as well as other information like your profile picture, your ranking at [www.slot.com](http://www.slot.com/), name, gender and achievements.

4\. WHAT PROCESSING WE DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL DATA AND FOR WHAT PURPOSES?

We want to be transparent with you and inform you about the operations we carry out with your data and the purposes for which we process such data.

First of all, we would like to inform you that the applicable data protection regulations require that for each processing of your data we have a database that legitimizes such processing. To process your personal information we are based in three legal foundations depending of the activity or treatment that we do with your data. We are based on the following ones to carry on with your personal data treatment:

  * Your agreement: Is possible that we activate offers or promotions that might be interesting for you. The participation or use of those promotions by the user is entirely voluntary, and it’s because of that that we are based on your agreement to treat your data in order to manage those promotional actions.

  * Our legitimate interest: We have a legitimate interest in collect your personal data for statistical purposes, as it provides us with the necessary information to improve your experience in the game in a more effective way. This requires that we carry out an analysis in which a balance is made of our interests in processing your personal data, with your rights and freedoms. The result of this analysis will determine whether or not we may use your personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy (except for processing related to the sending of commercial communications, for which we require your express consent).

We also have a legitimate interest of you knowing all the advantages that we will be introducing on the website through the sending of electronic communications in order to improve your experience on the game, so you can come back to our website to enjoy your favourite games.

In any case, we inform you that you may object to receiving commercial communications at any time, through the same email address unsubscribing or changing the setup of the newsletters or commercial communications found on the options of your profile.

  * Execution of the contract: To purchase virtual coins through our online store, you must expressly accept our Terms and Conditions governing such purchase, becoming part of the distance purchasing contract signed with us. You can check the terms of the contract on this link. We also use the execution of the contract to process your data in order to handle the requests for information you send us as well the management of your account as a user of Slot.com.

We would like to inform you that we will use the personal data you provide to us in the following ways:

4.1 Management of the Users accounts

  * We use your email account or Facebook in order to process your registration or any operation that you want to make with your account.

  * When you create your account, we take care that you receive a verification email to confirm that your have registered your account with your email address.

  * We handle your request to unsubscribe if you ask us to do so, by sending you an email confirming your unsubscription as a Slot.com user.

  * If we detect users who have a fraudulent behaviour, we will proceed to send and email informing about the inability to make any purchase.

4.2 Manage requests for information or queries you send us

  * We try to give you an answer as fast as we can at any request, suggestion or doubt that you send us through the online form.

  * We manage any incidence that you have detected on the website that prevents its correct functioning.

4.3 Manage and make easier the purchase of virtual coins

  * Our games include virtual coins or objects to use with our games. This virtual coin can be obtained for free or with his online purchase. We take care of the management of the purchase of the coins you purchase and solve any incidence related to that purchase.

4.4 Management of promotional actions and offers.

When you register to our website, we activate offers and promotional actions that we know that might be of your interest.

4.5 Analysis, segmentation and profiling of the user for sending promotional communications

We carry out with special campaigns and relevant promotions for you using techniques like profiling. The profiling is any form of automatic personal data treatment that consists in collecting all the data that we obtain of the game of the users.

We carry out with this profiling to offer you promotions or exclusive offers based on an analysis of your interests, preferences and activity on the game in slot.com.

In any case, we inform you that you may object to receiving commercial communications at any time, through the same email address unsubscribing or changing the setup of the newsletters or commercial communications found on the options of your profile.

4.6 Realization of statistical studies

We want to know if the games that we offer you in our website are of your interest. That’s why we make statistical studies about the purchases you do, the level of the game, the time that you are active to try to improve our service and your experience in our website.

If you don’t want that your personal data to be treated with statistical purposes, you only have to send us an email at [protecciondedatos@socialgamesonline.io](mailto:protecciondedatos@socialgamesonline.io)

5\. FOR HOW LONG WE SAVE YOUR PERSONAL DETAILS?

We will save your data while you don’t ask to delete your account from our website, and in any case during the time periods provided for by the applicable regulations regarding the limitation of liability.

6\. ¿CUÁLES SON TUS DERECHOS CUANDO NOS FACILITAS TUS DATOS PERSONALES? WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS WHEN YOU GIVE US YOUR PERSONAL DETAILS?

In order to make it easier, here are the rights you can exercise as a user of the website and App:

**Rights** | **What does it mean?**  
---|---  
**Right of access** | You have the right that Slot.com confirms you if it is treating or not your personal data, and what is the purpose for.  
**Right of correction** | It consists on the possibility of change those details that are nor exact or incomplete, you must indicate in the request for rectification which data you wish to be modified.  
**Right of opposition** | You can oppose at any time that we treat your data. You have the right to refuse at any time, for reasons related to your particular situation, to have personal data concerning you processed on the base of the legitimate interest of the company. Slot.com will stop treating your personal data unless we can prove compelling legitimate reasons for the processing that prevail over your interests, rights and freedoms, or for the formulation, exercise or defence of claims.  
**Right of cancellation** | This right allows you to cancel your personal data. The data will be blocked in a way that won’t allow its treatment without prejudice to their being made available to public administrations, judges and courts, for the purpose of dealing with possible liabilities resulting from processing during their limitation period.  
**Right to data portability** | You have the right to copy and transfer your personal data to another responsible of the treatment. Only it’s possible to use this right when the treatment is based on the execution of a contract or on your consent and the processing is carried out by automated means.  
**Right to the limitation of the treatment** | 

This right will allow you to ask us to stop processing your data when:

  * Dispute the accuracy of the data, while Slot.com verifies its accuracy.
  * You have exercised your right to refuse the processing of your data, while verifying whether the legitimate reasons of Slot.com prevail over yours as an interested party.

This right as well, allows you to ask Slot.com to conserve your personal data when:

  * The processing of data is illegal and as a data subject opposes the deletion of your data and requests instead a limitation of its use.
  * When Slot.com no longer need your personal details for processing purposes, but will be useful for formulation, exercise or defence of your claims.

**How to use this rights?** | 

You can use your right, sending us your request using the form available to you in the "help and contact" section or by post, by written and signed request, accompanied by a photocopy of your ID card or passport, to the following address: Ctra de Castellar, n.338, C.P 08226 Terrassa (Barcelona) – Ref. Protección de datos.

Also, we inform you that, when Slot.com has not properly satisfied the exercise of your rights, you can file a complaint with the Spanish Agency for Data Protection (AEPD). If you want to know more information about this right and how to exercise it, you can contact the AEPD:

Tel. 901 100 099 and 91.266.35.17

C/Jorge Juan,6 28001-Madrid  
  
7\. TO WHOM DO WE COMMUNICATE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?

Slot.com will not communicate to third parties your personal data unless its necessary for the provision of the contracted service such as communication to payment platforms, banks and companies so that transactions can be processed.

Unless for those necessary communications that should be carried out to give effect to the legal relationship maintained by Slot.com with the user, limiting in any case this communication to the purpose that justifies it.

It is also possible that we may communicate your personal data, subject to a legal requirement or basis that legitimizes the communication to courts or government agencies.

8\. PRIVACIDAD CHANGES ON THE PRESENT PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may change over time due to possible changes in the criteria followed by the supervisory authority responsible for data protection at any given time. Slot.com therefore reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to these criteria, as well as to new jurisprudential or legislative developments.

Last version: May 2018.

9\. DPO CONTACT

If you have any doubt about your personal data treatment, you can get in tough with the Delegate of Data Protection or sending an email to [protecciondedatos@socialgamesonline.io](mailto:protecciondedatos@socialgamesonline.io).
